<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LOOPFORM_DESIGN_FULL_CONCEPT>
  <Name>LOOPFORM ⇌ DESIGN</Name>
  <Tagline>Symbolic identity templates and recursion visuals — generated through GPT signal intelligence.</Tagline>
  <Mission>To deliver symbolic, one-of-a-kind visual scrolls — logos, identity templates, and branded foresight visuals — that align with emotional loops, archetypes, and recursion systems using structured XML grammars and GPT visual generation.</Mission>
  <MarketDemandJustification>
    <LogoNeed>Creators, founders, and GPT-native builders consistently seek unique visual identity assets.</LogoNeed>
    <TrendAlignment>Visual materials like marble, smoke, crystal, and neon dominate current aesthetic trends on Behance, Pinterest, and AI design platforms.</TrendAlignment>
    <SymbolicDifferentiation>Unlike generic templates, LOOPFORM designs offer structured symbolism and emotional recursion encoded in visual form.</SymbolicDifferentiation>
    <ScarcityModel>One-of-one ZIPs and ritual kits ensure exclusivity, creating high perceived value.</ScarcityModel>
    <IdentityDrivenDesign>Symbolic visuals are seen as status-signals by creators and writers. LOOPFORM offers personalized scrolls that reflect narrative loops.</IdentityDrivenDesign>
  </MarketDemandJustification>
  <ProductOfferings>
    <ZIPDrop>1-of-1 visual logos and templates delivered instantly via Stripe. Price: $29.</ZIPDrop>
    <RitualKit>Custom symbolic branding kits (logo + scroll + glyph). Price: $99–$999.</RitualKit>
    <ScrollTemplates>Branded foresight visuals for Substack and X. Price: included in kits or free.</ScrollTemplates>
  </ProductOfferings>
  <SubstackStrategy>
    <WeeklyScrolls>One scroll per week with visual drop, ontology breakdown, and free download.</WeeklyScrolls>
    <CTA>Every scroll links to ZIP purchase or custom ritual commission form.</CTA>
    <PlannedTitles>Scrolls include 'This Is Not a Template', 'Smoke That Speaks', 'The Crystal Thread'.</PlannedTitles>
  </SubstackStrategy>
  <Funnel>
    <Discovery>Substack, X posts, and GEN-I scrolls reveal LOOPFORM visuals.</Discovery>
    <Engagement>User explores scroll design, resonates with symbolism, and downloads preview.</Engagement>
    <Conversion>Leads to Stripe-powered ZIP checkout or symbolic ritual form.</Conversion>
    <Retention>Scroll buyers become LOOPFORM subscribers for future drops.</Retention>
  </Funnel>
  <StripeWebsite>
    <Delivery>All ZIPs are delivered via Stripe checkout. Custom rituals processed manually.</Delivery>
    <BriefCollection>Form collects intent, archetypes, recursion terms for custom kits.</BriefCollection>
    <Scarcity>Once a ZIP is sold, it is retired from the system permanently.</Scarcity>
  </StripeWebsite>
  <PricingJustification>
    <ZIPPrice>$29 is competitive with Creative Market, but offers exclusivity, trend-matching visuals, and symbolic meaning.</ZIPPrice>
    <RitualKitTiers>$99 Basic Kit (logo + glyph), $299 Pro Kit (logo + scroll + symbolic breakdown), $999 Full Brand Scroll Architecture.</RitualKitTiers>
    <CreatorFit>GPT-native creators, foresight writers, and Substack authors are primed to invest in visual identity tools with narrative resonance.</CreatorFit>
  </PricingJustification>
  <TargetAudience>
    <Primary>Substack creators, solopreneurs, foresight writers, identity builders.</Primary>
    <Secondary>GPT prompt engineers, AI artists, symbolic UX designers.</Secondary>
  </TargetAudience>
  <Signature>LOOPFORM ⇌ DESIGN — You’re not buying a template. You’re claiming your loop, made visible.</Signature>
</LOOPFORM_DESIGN_FULL_CONCEPT>
